Guide to the Jerome T. Barrett Collection, 1913-2010 LAC0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- The Friends of Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service History Archive, 1919-2010; Record Group 1; 68.5 Linear Feet
  - Directors and Commissioners, 1919-2010; Record Group 1 Series 1; 17 Linear Feet
    - Writings by Directors, Mediators and Employees, 1948 - 2007; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4; 1.5 Linear Feet
      - "Some Guidelines for Mediators of Intercultural Disputes", 1990 October; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 24)
        Published in Negotiation Journal.
      - "Labor Advocates Satisfaction in the Mediation Process Compared with their Satisfaction in the Arbitration Process", 1991; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 25)
        Author Clifford Crum
      - "Addressing Environmental Disputes with Labor Mediation Skills", 1992 September; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 26)
        Published in Arbitrations Journal.
      - "Realities of Interest Based (Win-Win) Bargaining", 1994 December; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - "Regulatory Negotiations: The Native American Experience", 1996; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 1)
        Authors: Jan Jung-Min Sunoo and Juliette Faulkner
      - "The Art and Practice of Alternative Dispute Resolutions", 1996 Febrary; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 2)
        Authors: Pamela Gentry DeSimone and Joel Schaffer
        Published in the journal California Public Employee Relations.
      - "New Models of Negotiation, Dispute Resolution, and Joint Problem Solving", 1996 April; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 3)
        Authors: John Calhoun Wells and Wilma Liebman
      - "Interest-Based Negotiation: An Engine-Driving Change", 1998 October; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 4)
        Authors: John Stepp, Kevin Sweeney, and Robert Johnson
        Published in The Journal for Quality and Participation.
      - "Is Interest-Based Bargaining Really News?", 2000 February; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        Published in Dispute Resolution Journal.
      - "In Whose Interest? A First Look at National Survey Data on Interest-Based Bargaining in Labor Relations", 2001 January; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 6)
        Authors: Joel Cutcher-Gershenfeld, Thomas Kochan, and John Calhoun Wells
      - "Point-Counterpoint: 'Win-Win' Bargaining", 2002; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 7)
        Authors: Ira Lobel and Janet Walden
        Published by the Center for Collaborative Solutions.
      - "Labor Relations and the International Arena", 2002 April; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 8)
        Authors: Ira Lobel and Brian Lobel
        Published in Dispute Resolution Journal
      - "The Justice Bazaar: Dispute Resolution through Emergent Private Ordering as a Superior Alternative to Authoritarian Court Bureaucracy", 2007; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 9)
        Author: Arthur Pearlstein
        Published in the Ohio State Journal on Dispute Resolution.
      - "Impact on Labor Relations of the PATCO Strike on its 25th Anniversary", 2007 February; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 10)
        Author: Kenneth Moffett
        Published in the Association of Labor Relations Agencies Advisor Newsletter.
      - "Mediation of Labor Disputes: Art, Science, or Misterie?", undated; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 11)
        Author: Leo Brown, SJ
      - "Organizing a Local Chapter of the Industrial Relations Research Association", 1965 October; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 12)
        Authors: T.R. Colsi and S.H. Sackman
      - "Mediation Techniques - To Minimize Rejections of Tentative Agreements Recommended by Union Committees", 1967 January 1; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - "Mediation: An Alternative to Violence", 1970; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 14)
        Author: Jerome T. Barrett
        Published in the Journal of Urban Law.
      - "Governmental Response to Public Unionism and the Recognition of Employee Rights", 1971; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 15)
        Reprinted from the Oregon Law Review.
      - "US Mediators Try a New Role", 1975 April 21; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 16)
      - "The Training and Development of Federal Mediators", 1977; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 17)
      - "Collective Bargaining in the Health Care Industry", 1979; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 18)
      - "The Psychology of a Mediator", 1983 March; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 19)
      - "The Law at the Bargaining Table", 1988 April; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 20)
        Author: Ted Chaskelson
      - "Toward Candor or Chaos: The Case of Confidentiality in Mediation", 1988 October 25; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 21)
        Author: Michael Prigoff
      - General Mediation Information, 1993 January 5; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 22)
        Author: Ed Sedlmeier
      - "The Origin of Mediation: The United States Conciliation Service in the US Department of Labor", 1995 November; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 23)
        Published by the Friends of the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service History.
      - "A Training Model to Improve the Effectiveness of a Labor-Management Committee", 2002; Record Group 1 Series 1 Suberies 4 (Box 19, Folder 24)
      - "The History of Joint Labor-Management Training: The FMCS Story", 2002 May; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 25)
        Published by the Friends of Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service History.
      - "Labor-Management Golden Years: A Foundation for Today's ADR", 2007; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 26)
        Published by the Association for Conflict Resolution.
      - "Interest Based Bargaining: A New Mediator Tool at FMCS", 2008 January; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 27)
      - "Sixty Years of FMCS: 1947 to 2007", 2008 January; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 28)
      - "New Era of Collective Bargaining and Mediation: 1980s and Since", 2008 April; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 29)
      - "The Role of Mediation and Conciliation in Collective Bargaining", undated; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 30)
      - "Collective Bargaining Negotiations from Management's Perspective", undated; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 4 (Box 19, Folder 31)
        Author: Frank Doyle
    - Mediator Biographies, 1946-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5; 1.5 Linear Feet
      The materials in this subseries are arranged in their original order, with each set of biographies arranged alphabetically.
      This subseries is comprised of biographical sketches of USCS conciliators, compiled from 1946-1951, and of FMCS mediators, compiled from 1960-1982. Included for each conciliator/mediator is a photograph, basic biographical information, education information, and employment experience prior to and with the USCS/FMCS. In addition, many include additions noting retired or deceased individuals.
      - USCS Biographies: A-G, 1946-1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 1)
      - USCS Biographies: H-M, 1946-1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 2)
      - USCS Biographies: N-S, 1946-1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 3)
      - USCS Biographies: T-Z, 1946-1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 4)
      - FMCS Biographies: Abner-Bradley, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 5)
      - FMCS Biographies: Brame-Curry, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 136, Folder 6)
      - FMCS Biographies: Davis-Fizer, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 1)
      - FMCS Biographies: Flores-Hennessy, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 2)
      - FMCS Biographies: Hermans-Kenealy, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 3)
      - FMCS Biographies: Kennedy-Lusk, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 4)
      - FMCS Biographies: MacDermott-Mize, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 137, Folder 5)
      - FMCS Biographies: Mlynek-Power, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - FMCS Biographies: Powers-Schultz, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - FMCS Biographies: Schwieger-Toner, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - FMCS Biographies: Trimble-Weggeland, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - FMCS Biographies: Weier-Zuiker, 1960-1982; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 5 (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Commissioners Handbooks, 1953 August 10 - 1972 June 3; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6; 2 Linear Feet
      This subseries is arranged into two parts. The first, in Boxes 13 and 14, contains two complete, bound copies of the FMCS Commissioners Handbook. The second, in Boxes 15 and 16, contains a third copy of the FMCS Commissioners Handbook, arranged in its original order.
      This subseries contains three copies of the FMCS Commissioners Handbook. The first belonged to Commissioner Robert T. Castrey and the second to the FMCS Pittsburgh Field Office. The third copy is not specifically labelled. While all three copies contain essentially the same materials, each is slightly different. A "Record of Revisions" in each copies reveals that each copy was edited independently and at different times between 1955 and 1972.
      The FMCS Commissioners Handbook contains a wide variety of information on the organization. Included is information on the FMCS' policies, procedures, budget, personnel and services. Also included are numerous forms used in the operation of the FMCS.
      - FMCS Commissioners Handbook of Commissioner Robert T. Castrey, 1953 August 10 - 1972 May 15; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - FMCS Commissioners Handbook of the Pittsburgh Field Office, 1953 August 10 - 1971 August 2; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - FMCS Commissioners Handbook: Record of Revisions, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Foreword, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Landmarks in Federal Mediation Activities, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Table of Contents, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Part 1: Organization of the Service, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Part 2: Policies and Procedures - Mediation, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Part 3: Policies and Procedures - Arbitration, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Part 4: Policies and Procedures - Administrative Management, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Personnel, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Budget and Finance [1/2], 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Budget and Finance [2/2], 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Services and Supply [1/2], 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Services and Supply [2/2], 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Part 5: Employee Rights and Responsibilities [1/2], 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Part 5: Employee Rights and Responsibilities [2/2], 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Part 6: Case Control Records and Procedures, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Appendix, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Forms Index, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - General Index, 1955 December 1 - 1972 June 6; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 6 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - United States Conciliation Service, 1919-1999; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7; 2 Linear Feet
      This subseries is arranged alphabetically.
      This subseries contains materials pertaining to the United States Conciliation Service, the Department of Labor's predecessor to the indepedent Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, dating from 1919-1999. Included are articles, reports, news clippings, correspondence, conference summaries, and material collected by or relating to Charles Estes and Walter Maggiolo.
      - "The Anvil and the Plow: A History of the U.S. Department of Labor", 1974; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 1)
      - Charles Estes Material [1/4], 1936-1947; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 2)
      - Charles Estes Material [2/4], 1946-1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 3)
      - Charles Estes Material [3/4], 1944-1946; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 4)
      - Charles Estes Material [4/4], 1946; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 5)
      - "The Conciliation Process", 1948 April; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 6)
      - "The Division of Conciliation: Its History, Activities and Organization", 1923; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 7)
      - Edgar Warren Articles, 1946-1948; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 8)
      - "Experiences with Cooperation Between Labor and Management in the Railway Industry", 1929; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 9)
      - Final Report of Director of Conciliation, 1947 August 21; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 10)
      - "The Foreman's Guide to Labor Relations", 1944; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 11)
      - Mediators and Staff Transferred on August 22, 1947, Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 12)
      - Miscellaneous USCS Documents, 1942-1999; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 134, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous USCS Documents, 1931-1976; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 13)
      - "Preliminary Investigation of a Procedure for Conditioning for Discussion" Masters Thesis, 1948 June; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 14)
      - Report: "The Role of Communication in the Improvement of Labor-Management Relations" [1/3], 1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 135, Folder 1)
      - Report: "The Role of Communication in the Improvement of Labor-Management Relations" [2/3], 1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 135, Folder 2)
      - Report: "The Role of Communication in the Improvement of Labor-Management Relations" [3/3], 1951; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 135, Folder 3)
      - Reverend Vincent I. Breen Dissertation [1/3], 1943; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 134, Folder 2)
        Submitted to the faculty of the School of Social Science of the Catholic University of America
      - Reverend Vincent I. Breen Dissertation [2/3], 1943; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 134, Folder 3)
      - Reverend Vincent I. Breen Dissertation [3/3], 1943; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 134, Folder 4)
      - Taft-Hartley Act, 1947-1948; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 15)
      - USCS Bibliography, 1941; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 163, Folder 16)
      - USCS Conference Summaries [1/3], 1946 March-May; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 134, Folder 5)
      - USCS Conference Summaries [2/3], 1946 March-May; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 134, Folder 6)
      - USCS Conference Summaries [3/3], 1946 July-November; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 134, Folder 7)
      - USCS Hearing Transcript, 1919 June 25; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 164, Folder 1)
      - Walter Maggiolo Material, 1943-1947; Record Group 1 Series 1 Subseries 7 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - General/Institutional, 1946-2010; Record Group 1 Series 2; 23.5 Linear Feet
    - Annual Reports, 1948-2010; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1; 2.5 Linear Feet
      This subseries is arranged chronologically by the year of each annual report.
      This subseries contains the annual reports of the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service from the years 1948-2010. Information contained within the reports includes each year's highlights, significant cases, analysis, and program/service information.
      - First Annual Report, 1948; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      - Second Annual Report, 1949; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      - Third Annual Report, 1950; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 3)
      - Fourth Annual Report, 1951; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      - Fifth Annual Report, 1952; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 5)
      - Sixth Annual Report, 1953; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Seventh Annual Report, 1954; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 7)
      - Eighth Annual Report, 1955; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 8)
      - Ninth Annual Report, 1956; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 9)
      - Tenth Annual Report, 1957; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 10)
      - Eleventh Annual Report, 1958; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 11)
      - Twelfth Annual Report, 1959; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 12)
      - Thirteenth Annual Report, 1960; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 13)
      - Fourteenth Annual Report, 1961; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 20, Folder 14)
      - Fifteenth Annual Report, 1962; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Sixteenth Annual Report, 1963; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Seventeenth Annual Report, 1964; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      - Eighteenth Annual Report, 1965; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 4)
      - Nineteenth Annual Report, 1966; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 5)
      - Twentieth Anniversary Report, 1967; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 6)
      - Twenty-first Annual Report, 1968; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 7)
      - Twenty-second Annual Report, 1969; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 8)
      - Twenty-third Annual Report, 1970; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 21, Folder 9)
      - Twenty-fourth Annual Report, 1971; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
      - Twenty-fifth Annual Report, 1972; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
      - Twenty-sixth Annual Report, 1973; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      - Twenty-seventh Annual Report, 1974; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      - Twenty-eighth Annual Report, 1975; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      - Twenty-ninth Annual Report, 1976; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      - Thirtieth Annual Report, 1977; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
      - Thirty-first Annual Report, 1978; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 8)
      - Thirty-second Annual Report, 1979; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 9)
      - Thirty-third Annual Report, 1980; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 10)
      - Thirty-fourth Annual Report, 1981; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 11)
      - Thirty-fifth Annual Report, 1982; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - Thirty-sixth Annual Report, 1983; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      - Thirty-seventh Annual Report, 1984; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      - Thirty-eighth Annual Report, 1985; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      - Thirty-ninth Annual Report, 1986; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      - Fortieth Annual Report, 1987; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 5)
      - Forty-first Annual Report, 1988; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - Forty-second Annual Report, 1989; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Forty-third Annual Report, 1990; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Forty-fourth and Forty-fifth Annual Reports, 1991-1992; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Forty-sixth and Forty-seventh Annual Reports, 1993-1994; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Forty-eighth Annual Report, 1995; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Forty-ninth Annual Report, 1996; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Fiftieth Annual Report, 1997; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Fifty-first Annual Report, 1998; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Fifty-second Annual Report, 1999; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Fifty-third Annual Report, 2000; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Fifty-fourth Annual Report, 2001; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 17)
      - Fifty-fifth Annual Report, 2002; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 23, Folder 18)
      - Fifty-sixth Annual Report, 2003; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      - Fifty-seventh Annual Report, 2004; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Fifty-eighth Annual Report, 2005; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Fifty-ninth Annual Report, 2006; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Sixtieth Annual Report, 2007; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Sixty-first Annual Report, 2008; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
      - Sixty-second Annual Report, 2009; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
      - Sixty-third Annual Report, 2010; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 1 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - FMCS Directories, 1951 January - 2008 June; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 2; 1.5 Linear Feet
      Note: the chronology re-starts with Box 71 Folder 8, as these materials were added after initial processing.
      This subseries is comprised of FMCS telephone, address and email directories dating from 1951-2008. Contact lists include FMCS offices and employees, various union locals and members of Congress.
      - Directory, 1951, 1951 January; Record Group 1 Series 2 Subseries 2 (Box 69, Folder 1)